ALEX DUDLEY

Knowledgeable security guard with over 12 years' experience protecting individuals and property. Capable of directing a security team and taking action in different situations, in cluding those that ca 11 for a rmed security. Profit ient in firearm use and safety as well as first (321) 345-6780 aid and CPR. Have communicated effectively with dozens of clients, assessing their security needs before recommending and implement! ng so lotions.

100 East First Street. Chicago. IL 60106 a.dud ley@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

LEAD SECURITY OFFICER

ACE Security Contractors, Chicago, IL November 2014- Present

- Train new security officers in company protocols, security best practices, and reporting duties
- Recommend subordinate officers for disciplinary action or promotion as appropriate
- Perform assessments of clients' needsand inspections of sites, facilities, and vehicles to be secured
- Coordinate and manage officers assigned to clients, both remotely andon-site
- Perform additional security tasks, such as patrolling and escort duties

SECURITY GUARD

Phoenix Security Solutions, Portland, OR October 2008- October 2014

- ♦ Patrolled clients' sites, watching for suspicious activities and individuals
- Intervened in situations when appropriate
- Perform ed mo n ito ri n g of sec u rity ca mera system s
- Kept track of authorized visitor I ogs when requested by clients

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Psychology University of Portland Portland, OR

September 2004 - June 2008

KEY SKILLS

- Secu ri ty a ssessm e nts
- Management of security personnel
- Armed and unarmed security proficiency

CERTIFICATIONS

- III i noi s con cea led ca rry lice nse, 2014 (renewed in 2019)
- ♦ Illinois firearm owner's i d enti ficati on ca rd, 2014
- 20-hour armed and unarmed III i noi s state secu rity certi ficati ons,
- First aid and CPR (renewed yearly)